

MELISSA ZANDMAN

WEB DEVELOPER

(510)-519-6638

www.melissazandman.com

hello@melissazandman.com

SUMMARY

Versatile web developer with a background in industrial engineering and a creative flair for coding and design. Made the move from Mexico to California in 2018 to embrace a software engineering career. Excited to join your team to deliver impactful web solutions prioritizing user experience.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Software Engineer Bootcamp Nucamp 2020

Software Engineer Fellowship Hackbright Academy 2019

Industrial Engineering Instituto Tecnologico de Ciudad Madero 2008-2012

SKILLS

HTML
CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind
Flask, jQuery, Jinja
Javascript (AJAX,JSON)
React JS, React Native
Python, NodeJS, Express
MongoDB, SQL
PostgreSQL
Git, GitHub, Bash (Command Line)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Client Success & Operations

Countable, San Francisco, CA | January 2022 - Present

- Reduced site development time by 79%, from 36.8 business days to 7.6 business days.
- Successfully launched over 15 client "impact" sites with meticulous attention to detail and high client satisfaction.
- Translated detailed Figma mocks into pixel-perfect implementations, ensuring precise outcomes.
- Demonstrated expertise in HTML, CSS, and delivering responsive and visually-appealing websites.
- Proactively addressed change requests from clients, providing efficient solutions.
- Supported team members in overcoming challenges and fostering a collaborative work environment.
- Recognized for meeting tight deadlines and exceeding performance expectations.
- Gained exposure to Agile/Scrum methodologies and JavaScript framework
- Initiated and developed a comprehensive Figma template, enabling seamless site creation for the team despite the absence of a dedicated product designer.

Solutions Engineer

Lenos Software, San Francisco | February 2019 - January 2022

- Identified feature requests and documentation gaps, enhancing support quality.
- Developed customized solutions, leading to a 15% increase in customer retention.
- Contributed to daily team meetings and fostered a collaborative work environment.
- Established strong cross-functional relationships with product management, sales and marketing, and engineering.